<blog>
	<post>
		<date>November 22, 2016</date>
		<author>Guy Ronen</author>
		<title>A first few tweaks toward a better Blogger</title>
		<link>https://blogger.googleblog.com/2016/11/a-first-few-tweaks-toward-better-blogger_22.html</link>
		<body>From New York to Jakarta, Blogger is one of the most popular ways to publish the things you’re passionate about. Still, we’ve heard that there’s more we can do to make the platform a better place to have your unique voice be heard. So we’ll be making some adjustments over time to bring you a faster, easier to use and more beautiful Blogger. To kick things off, we’ve taken a crack at simplifying Blogger’s dashboard so that it’s easier for you to get right to the tools you need.</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>May 06, 2016</date>
		<author>Jay Castro</author>
		<title>Keep your readers interested with the AdSense Guide to Audience Engagement</title>
		<link>https://blogger.googleblog.com/2016/05/keep-your-readers-interested-with.html</link>
		<body>Today, information is at our fingertips and we can access it from anywhere on any device. Just a few taps pull up millions of websites all competing for our attention. For bloggers, engaging with your audience has never been more important or more challenging. To help lay the foundation to a winning engagement strategy, the AdSense team created the AdSense Guide to Audience Engagement. Research shows that 29% of smartphone users will immediately switch to another site or app if it doesn’t satisfy their needs.</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>March 20, 2017</date>
		<author>Guy Ronen</author>
		<title>Share your unique style with new Blogger themes</title>
		<link>https://blogger.googleblog.com/2017/03/share-your-unique-style-with-new.html</link>
		<body>If you’re one of the millions of people who uses Blogger to share your views on current affairs, teach the world how to make sushi, or just offer a peek into your day, then you know how important it is to be able to put your personal stamp on your blog. After all, your blog isn’t just a place you share, it’s a reflection of who you are and the impression you’d like to leave with your readers. To make it easier for you to express your unique style, we’ve created a new set of blog themes for you to choose from.</body>
	</post>
</blog>